# <u>ÁNGEL VARGAS</u>

## SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a software developer, specialized in the field of application development. For the last 2 years, I have been developing applications using Node, Java programming languages and front-end frameworks like Angular. I am specializing in backend technologies and system design.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Java
- Spring boot
- Node.js
- SQL
- Angular
- Typescript
- Docker
- NoSQL

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Teamwork
- Communication
- Responsability
- Problem solving

#### **CONTACT**

Phone: +506 8410-7266 Email: angelvargaspersonal@gmail.com Linkedln: linkedin.com/in/angel-vargass/ GitHub: github.com/angelvargass Cartago, Costa Rica

## **EXPERIENCE**

## **Software Engineer**

#### Solarpunk

Developing a custom ERP for a well-known company in the abogacy industry using technologies such as: Angular, Node.js, MongoDB, MySQL and Docker.

November 2021 - Present

### Software development internship

#### 4Geeks

I joined this company to create an in-house product using the following technologies: Angular, Ruby on Rails, Docker, and PostgreSQL. Some responsibilities were creating tasks for the tickets, create unit test and talk with the client.

January 2021 - June 2021

## **EDUCATION**

#### Cenfotec

Bachelor degree in software engineering

2021 - Present

### Cenfotec

Technical degree in software development 2019 - 2020